{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"10.0.1","schemaVersion":"","author":"author","title":"","description":"project description","email":"author@company.com","website":"www.company.com","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":1500,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":11,"width":640,"height":480,"responsive":false,"scalable":false,"launchFile":"index.html"},"contentStructure":[{"id":"Text_Caption_331","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_331","title":"Cyber Security Awareness Month  Quiz ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_574","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_574","title":"Take our Security Quiz   to test your knowledge.    Click on Begin to start. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_575","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_575","title":"Brought to you by the Information Security Branch  Office of the Chief Information Officer ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_9","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si21887","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si21901","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide21706","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_331","Text_Caption_574","Text_Caption_575","Button_9","si21887","si21901"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide21706"}}},{"id":"Image_189","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_189","roles":{}},{"id":"si12441","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_338","roles":{}},{"id":"si12349","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_327","title":"1.\tTrue or False, It is a good idea to take stock (inventory) of all your electronic devices. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12360","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_328","title":"a) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12364","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_329","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12360_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si12382","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_332","title":"b) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12386","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_333","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12382_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si12435","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_337","roles":{}},{"id":"si12459","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_42","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12473","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_43","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19347","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19361","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19593","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19606","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19621","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19634","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19649","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19662","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19677","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19690","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12405","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_334","title":"Correct - Answer: A  You should regularly take stock of all your devices. Having an accurate, up-to-date device inventory will help you to keep track of type and age of devices. This can help you identify which devices need to be updated or patched and which devices you no longer need on your network.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12417","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_335","title":"Incorrect  - Answer: A  You should regularly take stock of all your devices. Having an accurate, up-to-date device inventory will help you to keep track of type and age of devices. This can help you identify which devices need to be updated or patched and which devices you no longer need on your network.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12429","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_336","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide12483","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_189","si12349","si12364","si12386","si12459","si12473","si19347","si19361","si19593","si19606","si19621","si19634","si19649","si19662","si19677","si19690","si12429"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide12483"},"question":{"interactionId":"12329","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"1.\tTrue or False, It is a good idea to take stock (inventory) of all your electronic devices.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["a"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_190","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_190","roles":{}},{"id":"si22070","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_714","roles":{}},{"id":"si21978","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_698","title":"2. True or False, MFA (Multi-factor authentication) should be chosen over a single password login. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21989","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_704","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21993","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_705","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21989_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_394","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22000","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_706","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22004","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_707","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22000_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_395","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22064","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_713","roles":{}},{"id":"si22092","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_103","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22110","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_104","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22132","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_105","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22150","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_106","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22162","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22174","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22186","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22198","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22210","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22222","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22234","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22246","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22034","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_710","title":"Correct - Answer: A  MFA is quickly replacing the password as a more secure way to manage our accounts and the information within. Multi-factor authentication is an authentication method in which a user is granted access only after successfully presenting two or more pieces of evidence in the form of knowledge, possession or biology. Some examples of evidence are passwords, fingerprints, eye scans, key cards, answers to questions and more. Always opt in for MFA whenever possible.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22046","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_711","title":"Incorrect - Answer: A  MFA is quickly replacing the password as a more secure way to manage our accounts and the information within. Multi-factor authentication is an authentication method in which a user is granted access only after successfully presenting two or more pieces of evidence in the form of knowledge, possession or biology. Some examples of evidence are passwords, fingerprints, eye scans, key cards, answers to questions and more. Always opt in for MFA whenever possible.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22058","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_712","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide22259","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_190","si21978","si21993","si22004","si22092","si22110","si22132","si22150","si22162","si22174","si22186","si22198","si22210","si22222","si22234","si22246","si22058"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide22259"},"question":{"interactionId":"21958","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"2. True or False, MFA (Multi-factor authentication) should be chosen over a single password login.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_191","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_191","roles":{}},{"id":"si22393","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_725","roles":{}},{"id":"si22301","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_699","title":"3.\t A complex password to keep your computer safe has which of the following characteristics? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22312","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_715","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22316","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_716","title":"10 Characters or more ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22312_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_397","roles":{"answer":{"title":"10 Characters or more\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22323","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_717","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22327","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_718","title":"Use Symbols ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22323_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_398","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Use Symbols\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24957","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24961","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Use numbers ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24957_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Use numbers\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24972","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24976","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Is unique ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24972_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Is unique\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si25421","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25425","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"All of the above ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25421_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"All of the above\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si22387","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_724","roles":{}},{"id":"si22415","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_107","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22433","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_108","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22455","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_109","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22473","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_110","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22485","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22497","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22509","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22521","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22533","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22545","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22557","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22569","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22357","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_721","title":"Correct - Answer: E  A strong password has at least 10 characters and uses symbols and numbers. Great passwords are unique to accounts so that if one account gets breached the other accounts will stay safe. If you struggle to remember your password try using a passphrase, which is simply a sequence of words.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22369","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_722","title":"Incorrect  - Answer: E  A strong password has at least 10 characters and uses symbols and numbers. Great passwords are unique to accounts so that if one account gets breached the other accounts will stay safe. If you struggle to remember your password try using a passphrase, which is simply a sequence of words.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22381","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_723","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide22582","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_191","si22301","si22316","si22327","si24961","si24976","si25425","si22415","si22433","si22455","si22473","si22485","si22497","si22509","si22521","si22533","si22545","si22557","si22569","si22381"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide22582"},"question":{"interactionId":"22281","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"3.\t A complex password to keep your computer safe has which of the following characteristics?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["E"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_192","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_192","roles":{}},{"id":"si22716","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_736","roles":{}},{"id":"si22624","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_700","title":"4. How can we use WI-FI safely? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22635","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_726","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22639","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_727","title":"Avoid handling confidential information while on a public network ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22635_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Avoid handling confidential information while on a public network\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22646","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_728","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22650","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_729","title":"Use a VPN (virtual private network) when doing work on public Wi-Fi ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22646_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Use a VPN (virtual private network) when doing work on public Wi-Fi\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si22657","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_730","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22661","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_731","title":"Monitor what devices connect to your network ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22657_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Monitor what devices connect to your network\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22928","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22932","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"All of the above ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22928_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"All of the above\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si22710","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_735","roles":{}},{"id":"si22738","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_111","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22756","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_112","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22778","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_113","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22796","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_114","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22808","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22820","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22832","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22844","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22856","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22868","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22880","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22892","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22680","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_732","title":"Correct -  Answer: D  To ensure WI-FI safety we should always avoid handling sensitive information when on a public network and opt for a VPN if we must connect to the public network. For your home devices, you should ensure that you are aware of what devices are connecting to your network and drop any that are unknown or unnecessary. If you are using a weak password for your network, then switch it out for a password that is 10 characters or more and uses numbers and symbols.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22692","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_733","title":"Incorrect  -  Answer: D  To ensure WI-FI safety we should always avoid handling sensitive information when on a public network and opt for a VPN if we must connect to the public network. For your home devices, you should ensure that you are aware of what devices are connecting to your network and drop any that are unknown or unnecessary. If you are using a weak password for your network, then switch it out for a password that is 10 characters or more and uses numbers and symbols.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22704","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_734","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide22905","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_192","si22624","si22639","si22650","si22661","si22932","si22738","si22756","si22778","si22796","si22808","si22820","si22832","si22844","si22856","si22868","si22880","si22892","si22704"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide22905"},"question":{"interactionId":"22604","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"4. How can we use WI-FI safely?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_193","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_193","roles":{}},{"id":"si23144","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_749","roles":{}},{"id":"si23041","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_701","title":"5.  True or False, if you fall for a phishing text message and you click on a malicious link or attachment, you will know right away. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23052","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_737","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23056","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_738","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23052_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23063","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_739","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23067","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_740","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23063_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si23138","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_748","roles":{}},{"id":"si23166","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_115","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23184","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_116","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23206","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_117","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23224","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_118","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23236","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23248","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23260","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23272","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23284","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23296","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23308","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23320","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23108","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_745","title":"Correct - Answer: B  Many phishing attacks have invisible malicious effects. Malicious links can take you to a page that looks almost exactly like a real login page and will try to trick you into entering your login information. Malicious attachments might spread a virus that operates invisibly in the background. Make sure to first identify what the hidden link is on a text message by holding down the linked text, selecting copy url, then pasting the URL into a document.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23120","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_746","title":"Incorrect  - Answer: B  Many phishing attacks have invisible malicious effects. Malicious links can take you to a page that looks almost exactly like a real login page and will try to trick you into entering your login information. Malicious attachments might spread a virus that operates invisibly in the background. Make sure to first identify what the hidden link is on a text message by holding down the linked text, selecting copy url, then pasting the URL into a document.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23132","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_747","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide23333","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_193","si23041","si23056","si23067","si23166","si23184","si23206","si23224","si23236","si23248","si23260","si23272","si23284","si23296","si23308","si23320","si23132"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide23333"},"question":{"interactionId":"23021","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"5.  True or False, if you fall for a phishing text message and you click on a malicious link or attachment, you will know right away.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_194","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_194","roles":{}},{"id":"si23482","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_763","roles":{}},{"id":"si23379","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_750","title":"6.  True or false, you should place smart devices on a separate network? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23390","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_751","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23394","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_752","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23390_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_407","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si23401","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_753","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23405","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_754","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23401_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_408","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23476","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_762","roles":{}},{"id":"si23504","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_119","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23522","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_120","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23544","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_121","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23562","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_122","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23574","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23586","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23598","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23610","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23622","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23634","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23646","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23658","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23446","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_759","title":"Correct - Answer:  A   A separate network is a good idea if you have lots of friends dropping by and jumping on your network, or if you have lots of home smart devices. Smart devices are often less secure then our computers and laptops. If your smart devices are connected to the main network and they get compromised, intruders can also get into your other devices that hold your confidential and financial information.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23458","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_760","title":"Incorrect  - Answer: A   A separate network is a good idea if you have lots of friends dropping by and jumping on your network, or if you have lots of home smart devices. Smart devices are often less secure then our computers and laptops. If your smart devices are connected to the main network and they get compromised, intruders can also get into your other devices that hold your confidential and financial information.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23470","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_761","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide23671","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_194","si23379","si23394","si23405","si23504","si23522","si23544","si23562","si23574","si23586","si23598","si23610","si23622","si23634","si23646","si23658","si23470"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide23671"},"question":{"interactionId":"23359","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"6.  True or false, you should place smart devices on a separate network?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_195","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_195","roles":{}},{"id":"si23820","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_777","roles":{}},{"id":"si23717","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_764","title":"7.  What is the best Wi-Fi router security? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23728","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_765","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23732","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_766","title":"Wi-Fi Protected Access (WPA)  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23728_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_411","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Wi-Fi Protected Access (WPA) \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23739","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_767","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23743","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_768","title":"Wi-Fi Protected Access II (WPA2) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23739_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_412","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Wi-Fi Protected Access II (WPA2)\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si23750","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_769","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23754","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_770","title":"Wired Equivalent Privacy (WEP) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23750_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"399_413","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Wired Equivalent Privacy (WEP)\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24830","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24834","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Wired Protected Elite (WPE) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24830_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Wired Protected Elite (WPE)\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si25436","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25440","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Wi-Fi Protected Alpha (WPA) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25436_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Wi-Fi Protected Alpha (WPA)\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23814","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_776","roles":{}},{"id":"si23842","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_123","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23860","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_124","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23882","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_125","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23900","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_126","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23912","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23924","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23936","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23948","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23960","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23972","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23984","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23996","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23784","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_773","title":"Correct - Answer:  B  WPA2, is currently the most secure choice.  Check the ‘wireless security’ or ‘wireless network’ settings page in your router’s administration console for your encryption type. Temporal Key Integrity Protocol (TKIP) and Advanced Encryption Standard (AES) are the two different types of encryption you’ll see used on networks secured with WPA2.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23796","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_774","title":"Incorrect  -  Answer:  B  WPA2, is currently the most secure choice.  Check the ‘wireless security’ or ‘wireless network’ settings page in your router’s administration console for your encryption type. Temporal Key Integrity Protocol (TKIP) and Advanced Encryption Standard (AES) are the two different types of encryption you’ll see used on networks secured with WPA2.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23808","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_775","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide24009","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_195","si23717","si23732","si23743","si23754","si24834","si25440","si23842","si23860","si23882","si23900","si23912","si23924","si23936","si23948","si23960","si23972","si23984","si23996","si23808"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide24009"},"question":{"interactionId":"23697","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"7.  What is the best Wi-Fi router security?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_201","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_201","roles":{}},{"id":"si25607","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_825","roles":{}},{"id":"si25493","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_794","title":"8.  When getting a new smart device you find that it has many great settings and features. What should you do with these settings? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25504","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_811","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25508","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_812","title":"Trust the manufacturer and leave them on the default settings. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25504_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_429","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Trust the manufacturer and leave them on the default settings.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si25515","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_813","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25519","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_814","title":"Change all the default settings and turn everything off.device. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25515_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_430","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Change all the default settings and turn everything off.device.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si25526","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_815","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25530","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_816","title":"Change all the default settings and turn everything on. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25526_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"399_431","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Change all the default settings and turn everything on.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si25537","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_817","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25541","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_818","title":"Take the time to learn what each setting and feature means for your  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25537_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"432","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Take the time to learn what each setting and feature means for your \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si25601","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_824","roles":{}},{"id":"si25629","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_133","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide25796q7","for":"Slide25796q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25647","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_134","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide25796q7","for":"Slide25796q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25669","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_135","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide25796q7","for":"Slide25796q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25687","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_136","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide25796q7","for":"Slide25796q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25699","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide25796q7","for":"Slide25796q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25711","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide25796q7","for":"Slide25796q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25723","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide25796q7","for":"Slide25796q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25735","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide25796q7","for":"Slide25796q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25747","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide25796q7","for":"Slide25796q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25759","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide25796q7","for":"Slide25796q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25771","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide25796q7","for":"Slide25796q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25783","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide25796q7","for":"Slide25796q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25571","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_821","title":"Correct - Answer: D  Smart devices come with many great settings and features and are updated constantly. When you get a new device, you are likely going see many new features and different setting configurations. Not every manufacturer sets the defaults with your privacy and security in mind. Make sure you understand what the settlings mean to ensure that you are sharing the least amount of information and access privileges.    Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25583","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_822","title":"Incorrect  -  Answer: D  Smart devices come with many great settings and features and are updated constantly. When you get a new device, you are likely going see many new features and different setting configurations. Not every manufacturer sets the defaults with your privacy and security in mind. Make sure you understand what the settlings mean to ensure that you are sharing the least amount of information and access privileges.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25595","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_823","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide25796","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_201","si25493","si25508","si25519","si25530","si25541","si25629","si25647","si25669","si25687","si25699","si25711","si25723","si25735","si25747","si25759","si25771","si25783","si25595"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide25796"},"question":{"interactionId":"25473","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"8.  When getting a new smart device you find that it has many great settings and features. What should you do with these settings?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_185","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_185","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_107","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_107","title":"Quiz Results ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6059","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6083","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6091","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6055","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You Scored: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6079","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Total Questions: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6087","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Accuracy: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6103","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6107","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6121","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20489","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20502","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20517","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20530","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide6038","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6038"}}},{"id":"si6231","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_186","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_186","roles":{}},{"id":"Button_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_4","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19054","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19068","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_9","title":" Stay Current With Information Security By Subscribing to the:   Weekly Security News Digest ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_298","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_298","title":"Thank you for taking the quiz.  To exit the quiz, close the browser window. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide6219","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si6231","Image_186","Button_4","si19054","si19068","SmartShape_9","Text_Caption_298"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":600},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6219"}}},{"id":"Pool502","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":502,"name":"Pool1","questions":[]}}},{"id":"October2020Quiz","class":"project","title":"October2020Quiz","children":["Slide21706","Slide12483","Slide22259","Slide22582","Slide22905","Slide23333","Slide23671","Slide24009","Slide25796","Slide6038","Slide6219"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":458,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":true,"questions":["Slide12483q0","Slide22259q1","Slide22582q2","Slide22905q3","Slide23333q4","Slide23671q5","Slide24009q6","Slide25796q7"],"minScore":0,"maxScore":80,"passScore":64}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":false},"toc":{"enabled":false},"playbar":{"enabled":true,"cc":false,"playPause":true,"back":true,"forward":true,"rewind":true,"close":true,"mute":true,"progressBar":true}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"quiz","CCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"SCCriteria":"quiz","SCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"exitNormalIfCompleted":false},"toc":[{"id":"Slide21706","title":"Slide 1"},{"id":"Slide12483","title":"Slide 2"},{"id":"Slide22259","title":"Slide 3"},{"id":"Slide22582","title":"Slide 4"},{"id":"Slide22905","title":"Slide 5"},{"id":"Slide23333","title":"Slide 6"},{"id":"Slide23671","title":"Slide 7"},{"id":"Slide24009","title":"Slide 8"},{"id":"Slide25796","title":"Slide 9"},{"id":"Slide6038","title":"Slide 10"},{"id":"Slide6219","title":"Slide 11"}]}